

PROFILE

A fast learner, possesses good written and verbal communication skills and excellent interpersonal skills with good leadership and teamwork ability; who wishes to play a vital role in a progressive, forward thinking organization, and the opportunity to utilize knowledge and experiences effectively.

CONTACT

Mob: +8801671 850 570

www.linkedin.com/in/ziaur-rahmansiddiqui-b9b31714b/

EMAIL:

ziasiddiqui.23@gmail.com

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Nationality: Bangladeshi

Date of Birth: 23rd May 1993

Height: 5'8

Blood Group: B+

Religion: Muslim

Interests: Motorcycling,

Photography, Travelling.

ZIAUR RAHMAN SIDDIQUI

EDUCATION

Independent University Bangladesh

Bachelor of Social Science in Media and Communication Class of 2017 CGPA 3.24

GED

Private Candidate – American Alumni Association

Year: 2012

Oxford International School

O' Levels (CIE) Year: 2008

WORK EXPERIENCE

Adcomm Limited- Senior Executive, Brand Service

From 01 July 2019 till date.

Adcomm Limited- Executive, Brand Service

From 01 January 2018 to 30 June 2019

Film Noir- Assistant Director

From 23 October 2015 to 31 December 2017

BRANDS HANDLED AS A CLIENT SERVICE

Ispahani (Tea, Foods & Agro), Social Marketing Company (SMC),

City Group, Orion footwear,

Singer,

Coca-Cola,

Super Star Group (SSG),

bproperty, RFL Shine.

Akij Bakers Limited,

Kallol Group (MAMA Noodles, Nutri-C, Credence, Jet),

Turkish Airlines,

Bangladesh Honda Private Limited (BHL)

Bangladesh Motorcycle Assemblers & Manufacturers Association

(BMAMA).

SUCCESSFUL CAMPAIGNS

SKILLS & ACTIVITIES

Understands basics of Digital Marketing.

Microsoft Office Suit:

MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, MS

Word.

Language skills:

Fluent in Bengali & English Understands: Hindi & Urdu

Volunteer:

Volunteering for Bangladesh, Jagoo, One Degree Initiative, Bhaatbank.

Member of Photography club and Environmental club of IUB.

Certification:

Basic Photography course from "Pathshala."

- Ispahani Banglabid
- Ispahani Mirzapore Thematic
- Ispahani New Normal Life
- Ispahani Immunity Boosting
- ISPI Thematic
- Little Bite Thematic
- TEER Mother's Day
- TEER Little Chef (Season 1 & 2)
- Orion Winter Campaign
- Orion Back to school
- Orion Never be the same
- Orion Pohela Boishakh
- SSG Light Alo Hok Valo
- BMAMA Rastai Choli Asthai
- SMC Pink Star Network
- SMC Green Star Network
- SMC Blue Star Network
- SMC Floating IEC
- SMC MoniMix
- SMC Vermicid
- Fay Hand Sanitizer Launching